<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pc version="PF">
<character><name>Sarah</name>
<uniqueID>1011</uniqueID>
<edition>2</edition>
<xp>0</xp>
<race><name>Halfling</name><size>3</size><feat><name>Halfling Traits</name><text>+2 Dexterity, +2 Charisma, –2 Strength: Halflings are nimble and strong-willed, but their small stature makes them weaker than other races.

Small: Halflings are Small creatures and gain a +1 size bonus to their AC, a +1 size bonus on attack rolls, a –1 penalty to their CMB and CMD, and a +4 size bonus on Stealth checks.

Fearless: Halflings receive a +2 racial bonus on all saving throws against fear. This bonus stacks with the bonus granted by halfling luck.

Halfling Luck: Halflings receive a +1 racial bonus on all saving throws.

Keen Senses: Halflings receive a +2 racial bonus on Perception checks.

Fleet of Foot: Some halflings are quicker than their kin but less cautious. Halflings with this racial trait move at normal speed and have a base speed of 30 feet. This racial trait replaces slow speed and sure-footed.

Weapon Familiarity: Halflings are proficient with slings and treat any weapon with the word &#34;halfling&#34; in its name as a martial weapon.</text><expanded>0</expanded><modifier><category>1</category><value>-2</value></modifier><modifier><category>1</category><type>1</type><value>2</value></modifier><modifier><category>1</category><type>5</type><value>2</value></modifier><modifier><category>2</category><type>31</type><value>4</value></modifier><modifier><type>22</type></modifier><modifier><category>2</category><type>24</type><value>2</value></modifier></feat></race>
<class><name>Brawler</name><level>3</level><hd>3</hd><baseAttack>3</baseAttack><fortitude>3</fortitude><reflex>3</reflex><will>1</will><slots>0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slots><slotsCurrent>0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</slotsCurrent><modifier><name>Hit Points: 10 + 6/level</name><type>18</type><value>22</value></modifier><modifier><name>Favored Class</name><type>18</type><value>3</value></modifier><feat><name>Animal Companion</name><text>Link (Ex): A druid can handle her animal companion as a free action, or push it as a move action, even if she doesn&#39;t have any ranks in the Handle Animal skill. The druid gains a +4 circumstance bonus on all wild empathy checks and Handle Animal checks made regarding an animal companion.

Evasion (Ex): If an animal companion is subjected to an attack that normally allows a Reflex save for half damage, it takes no damage if it makes a successful saving throw.</text><expanded>0</expanded><modifier><category>2</category><type>10</type><value>4</value></modifier></feat><feat><name>Brawler&#39;s Flurry</name><text>Starting at 2nd level, a brawler can make a brawler&#39;s flurry as a full-attack action. When doing so, a brawler has the Two-Weapon Fighting feat when attacking with any combination of unarmed strikes, weapons from the close fighter weapon group, or weapons with the &#34;monk&#34; special feature. She does not need to use two different weapons to use this ability.

A brawler applies her full Strength modifier to her damage rolls for all attacks made with brawler&#39;s flurry, whether the attacks are made with an off-hand weapon or a weapon wielded in both hands. A brawler can substitute disarm, sunder, and trip combat maneuvers for unarmed attacks as part of brawler&#39;s flurry. A brawler with natural weapons can&#39;t use such weapons as part of brawler&#39;s flurry, nor can she make natural weapon attacks in addition to her brawler&#39;s flurry attacks.</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat><feat><name>Martial Flexibility</name><text>A brawler can take a move action to gain the benefit of a combat feat she doesn&#39;t possess. This effect lasts for 1 minute. The brawler must meet all the feat&#39;s prerequisites. She may use this ability a number of times per day equal to 3 + 1/2 her brawler level (minimum 4 times per day).

The brawler can use this ability again before the duration expires to replace the previous combat feat with another choice.

If a combat feat has a daily use limitation (such as with Stunning Fist), any uses of that combat feat while using this ability count toward that feat&#39;s daily limit.</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat><feat><name>Maneuver Training</name><text>At 3rd level, a brawler can select one combat maneuver to receive additional training. She gains a +1 bonus on combat maneuver checks when performing that combat maneuver and a +1 bonus to her CMD when defending against that maneuver.

Whenever the wild child chooses a new maneuver for this ability, his animal companion also learns a trick that makes use of this combat maneuver.</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat></class>
<hpMax>6</hpMax><hpCurrent>31</hpCurrent><hpTemp>0</hpTemp><abilitySTR>10</abilitySTR><abilityDEX>10</abilityDEX><abilityCON>10</abilityCON><abilityINT>10</abilityINT><abilityWIS>10</abilityWIS><abilityCHA>10</abilityCHA><skillPoints>12</skillPoints><spellsCount>0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</spellsCount><spellsPerDay>0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,</spellsPerDay><skill><name>Bluff</name><ability>6</ability><skillID>2</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Perception</name><ability>5</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>24</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Craft*</name><ability>4</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>4</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (planes)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>21</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Spellcraft</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>30</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Ride</name><ability>2</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>27</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Use Magic Device</name><ability>6</ability><skillID>34</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Stealth</name><ability>2</ability><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>31</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Climb</name><ability>1</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>3</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Disguise</name><ability>6</ability><skillID>7</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Acrobatics</name><ability>2</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (arcana)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>13</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Intimidate</name><ability>6</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>12</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Diplomacy</name><ability>6</ability><skillID>5</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Disable Device</name><ability>2</ability><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>6</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Sleight of Hand*</name><ability>2</ability><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>29</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Swim</name><ability>1</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>33</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Handle Animal*</name><ability>6</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>10</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Heal</name><ability>5</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>11</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Fly</name><ability>2</ability><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>9</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (local)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>18</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (history)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>17</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (nature)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>19</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Sense Motive</name><ability>5</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><skillID>28</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Survival</name><ability>5</ability><skillID>32</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Knowledge (religion)</name><ability>4</ability><skillID>22</skillID></skill>
<skill><name>Escape Artist</name><ability>2</ability><classSkill>1</classSkill><armorPenalty>1</armorPenalty><skillID>8</skillID></skill>
<action><name>Brawler&#39;s Flurry</name><damage>1w+%1x2</damage><attack>%9-2</attack></action>
<tracker><label>Martial Flexibility</label><resetType>1</resetType><value>4</value><formula>4</formula></tracker><item><name>Unarmed Strike</name><slot>2</slot><type>3</type><damage>1d4</damage><damageType>1</damageType><text>A brawler may attack with fists, elbows, knees, and feet. This means that a brawler may make unarmed strikes with her hands full. A brawler applies her full Strength modifier (not half) on damage rolls for all her unarmed strikes.

Usually, a brawler&#39;s unarmed strikes deal lethal damage, but she can choose to deal nonlethal damage instead with no penalty on her attack roll. She has the same choice to deal lethal or nonlethal damage while grappling.

A brawler&#39;s unarmed strike is treated as both a manufactured weapon and a natural weapon for the purposes of spells and effects that modify either manufactured weapons or natural weapons.</text></item>
<item><src>2</src><edition>2</edition><name>Gold Pieces</name><slot>-1</slot><type>17</type><damage>1d4</damage><weight>0.02</weight><quantity>890</quantity><text></text></item>
<item><src>2</src><edition>2</edition><name>Chain Shirt</name><slot>5</slot><type>0</type><armorClass>4</armorClass><maxDexterity>4</maxDexterity><armorPenalty>2</armorPenalty><damage>1d4</damage><weight>12.5</weight><text>Covering the torso, this shirt is made up of thousands of interlocking metal rings.</text></item>
<note><title>Tricks (8)</title><text>Tah-dah</text><expanded>0</expanded></note>
<note><title>To-do List</title><text>Sarah
(1) Picks 2 feats
(2) Assign ability scores
(3) Assign skill ranks
(4) Buy gear

Hyena
(1) Pick two feats
(2) Assign skill ranks
(3) Choose tricks</text></note>
<feat><name>Combat Expertise (1st)</name><text>You can choose to take a –1 penalty on melee attack rolls and combat maneuver checks to gain a +1 dodge bonus to your Armor Class. When your base attack bonus reaches +4, and every +4 thereafter, the penalty increases by –1 and the dodge bonus increases by +1. You can only choose to use this feat when you declare that you are making an attack or a full-attack action with a melee weapon. The effects of this feat last until your next turn.</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat>
<feat><name>Improved Unarmed Strike (1st)</name><text>You are considered to be armed even when unarmed—you do not provoke attacks of opportunity when you attack foes while unarmed. Your unarmed strikes can deal lethal or nonlethal damage, at your choice.</text><expanded>0</expanded></feat>
<companion>1012</companion>
<imageData><uniqueID>1020</uniqueID></imageData></character>
</pc>
